{"description":"A set of questions to test the software with","name":"Loadmaster All","version":1,"questions":[{"question":"1. To override the #2 or #3 hydraulic aux pumps for an auto shutdown due to low quantity or overheat,","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Fig. 1 -160 S2]","responses":["Press and hold appropriate Aux pump switch for 5 seconds. ","Press and hold XFER pump switch for 5 seconds ","Press and hold appropriate Aux pump switch for 3 seconds ","Press and hold appropriate Aux pump switch for 5 seconds. "]},{"question":"2. When the APU alert start feature is used, there will be no _____ until the battery bus is powered.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 1 -179(C)]","responses":["fuel flow ","available power ","fire detection or protection ","emergency exit lights"]},{"question":"3. The Battery Direct Bus, the Battery Bus, the AC and DC Emergency Buses, and the AC and DC Transfer Buses comprise the .","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 1 -351]","responses":["electrical power system ","battery power system ","external power system ","emergency power system "]},{"question":"4. To preclude damage to the landing gear, accomplish no more than _____ consecutive landings without a cooling period. A cooling period consists of, flying with the gear retracted for at least 20 minutes or with the gear extended for at least 10 minutes before the next landing.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 5 -110]","responses":["two","three","four","five"]},{"question":"5. The Maximum Payload for the C -17 is _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 1 -8]","responses":["Maximum Takeoff Weight minus Operating Weight. ","Maximum Takeoff Weight minus Ramp Fuel Weight. ","Zero Fuel Weight minus Operating Weight. ","Basic Aircraft Weight minus Operating Weight "]},{"question":"6. A WAP message, CREW OXY LOW will be displayed when quantity is less than 5 liters or supply pressure is below _____ +\/- 5 psi.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 1 -2296]","responses":["7.5","60","285","430 "]},{"question":"7. Following an intentional cabin depressurization above 10,000 feet, the cabin must be repressurized to less than _____ feet to reset the regulators. If the regulators are not reset, subsequent flight above 9,000 feet cabin altitude may deploy the passenger oxygen masks.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 1 -2318(N)","responses":["3,500","8,000","8,500","12,500 "]},{"question":"8. Below _____ feet cabin altitude, each emergency oxygen regulator SURGE MODE lever\/three position toggle switch must be positioned to MAN ON\/MANUAL ON to provide passenger oxygen.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 1 -2319]","responses":["25,000","20,000","15,000","12,500 "]},{"question":"9. The passenger oxygen masks can be manually deployed at any altitude with the -1 emergency oxygen regulator by positioning the SURGE MODE lever to the MAN ON position and rotating the spring loaded surge knob _____ and holding momentarily (approximately _____ seconds) to open the passenger oxygen\t \t containers and start the flow of oxygen.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 1 -2319]","responses":["clockwise; 3 ","counter clockwise; 3 ","clockwise; 6 ","counter clockwise; 6 "]},{"question":"10. If either the pilot\u2019s or loadmaster\u2019s FED ARM switch is in ARM, all four FEDS hatches can be deployed from either the _____ initiator handles.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 1 -2336]","responses":["pilots overhead panel or the aft left loadmaster station ","pilots overhead panel or the maintenance\/ditching hatch ","forward loadmaster station or the aft left loadmaster station ","maintenance\/ditching hatch or the forward loadmaster station "]},{"question":"11. Portable hand fire extinguishers are provided in the following areas; _____ in the Cockpit, _____ in the Crew rest area, and _____ in the Cargo compartment.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 1 -2348]","responses":["2; 1; 6 ","1; 2; 6 ","2; 0; 7 ","1; 1; 7 "]},{"question":"12. The EEBD is a _____-minute self-contained, disposable breathing unit. There are ______ installed on the aircraft.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 1 -2353, 1 -2351]","responses":["15; 4 ","20; 4 ","15; 6 ","20; 6"]},{"question":"14. During the Interior Safety Inspection - Power Off, failure to fully install safety switch pins or place CMDS WOW MAINT ORIDE switch to NORM could _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 2 -29(W)]","responses":["a partial ejection of flares ","an unintended jettison of payloads ","an unsuccessful deployment of flares ","a misfire or burn in place after firing of flares "]},{"question":"15. If the aircraft is powered by batteries alone and the pilot\u2019s CNC indicates OFF, radio communication is possible using the _______ radio with the VHF\/UHF Backup Control panel.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 2 -29(N)]","responses":["COM 1 ","COM 2 ","UHF ","VHF "]},{"question":"16. The loadmaster advises the medical crew director that seat belts are required _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 2 -53]","responses":["at the briefing ","immediately prior to engine start ","immediately prior to taxi ","immediately prior to takeoff "]},{"question":"17. The purge valve on the flight crew quick don mask should be in the _________ position except during preflight and\t when oxygen is in use where smoke or fumes are not present and goggles are not required.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 2 -795(N)]","responses":["CLOSED ","OPEN ","STOWED ","DEPLOYED "]},{"question":"18. During in-flight operation of the troop doors, deploy the air deflector between \t _____ and _____ degrees before opening the first door.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 2 -882]","responses":["5; 10 ","10; 15 ","15; 20 ","fully deployed "]},{"question":"19. When on\/offloading vehicles, do not deflate vehicle pneumatic tires _________.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 2 -962(C)]","responses":["at any time ","to decrease PSI ","to reduce the need for shoring ","below the tires rated inflation pressure "]},{"question":"20. Equipment mounted on a single axle disconnected from its prime mover and loaded with its tongue resting on the aircraft floor or ramp, _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 2 -966]","responses":["must be drained and purged ","must be drained, but not purged ","may be transported with fuel in tank not to exceed 1\/2 tank ","may be transported with fuel in tank not to exceed 3\/4 tank "]},{"question":"21. When the vehicle is parked on the cargo floor and parking brakes are _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 2 -966]","responses":["install a minimum of one chock, aft of the tires ","install a minimum of two chocks, one forward and one aft of the tires ","install a minimum of two chains and two tiedown devices, one forward and one aft ","install a minimum of one chain to prevent the vehicle from rolling out of the aircraft "]},{"question":"22. When loading pallets with a bare tine forklift, one set of inner roller channels may be removed from the ramp toes if the pallet weight does not exceed _____ pounds.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"T.O. 1C -17A -1 [Para. 2 -964]","responses":["8,400","8,500","9,100","10,355 "]},{"question":"23. Except where prohibited by specific procedures, open circuit breakers _____ in the event that the electrical condition was transient in nature.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 3 -19]","responses":["may continuously be reset ","may be reset once ","may be reset twice ","may be reset once an hour "]},{"question":"24. If both left and right side FEDS Shielded Mild Detonating Cord (SMDC) lines are inoperative (AA- EM w\/o TCTO 1549), limit persons on board to a maximum of _____ when mission segments involve overwater flight.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 3 -497 (N)]","responses":["158","138","92","61 "]},{"question":"25. The signal for prepare for ditching or crash landing is","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 3 -27]","responses":["3 short rings of the alarm bell ","3 long rings of the alarm bell ","6 short rings of the alarm bell ","6 long rings of the alarm bell "]},{"question":"26. All odors not identifiable by the flight crew shall be considered toxic. Immediately _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 3 -29]","responses":["descend to below FL250 and decrease airspeed. ","use 100% oxygen, ventilate the aircraft, and land as soon as practical. ","have the loadmaster inspect all cargo for leaks and consider using 100% oxygen. ","depress the DROP switchlight twice and direct passengers to use oxygen masks. "]},{"question":"27. Following a ditching emergency, as a minimum, the loadmaster will provide _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Fig. 3 -38]","responses":["a classified data case and igloo ","a first aid kit and igloo ","a flashlight and classified data case. ","a flashlight and first aid kit "]},{"question":"28. If a fire is being fed by oxygen from an oxygen system, consider turning off the _____ until the fire is suppressed.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 3 -217(W)]","responses":["CRU\/73A regulator ","-501 emergency regulator ","manual shutoff valves ","HALO\/therapeutic regulator "]},{"question":"29. Selective freefall of any landing gear can be accomplished by activating the release handles only for those\t \t gear that are not extended. When lowering both main gear on one side, lower _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 3 -432(N)]","responses":["both gear simultaneously ","the forward gear first ","the aft gear first ","the nose gear first "]},{"question":"30. During the Loadmaster Ground Emergency Procedure, you need to notify the fire department by any available means. State the _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 3 -535]","responses":["Nature of the emergency, tail number, parking spot number, number of personnel on board ","Nature of the emergency, parking spot number, number of personnel on board, damage incurred ","Parking spot number, time of incident, number of personnel on board, damage incurred ","Number of personnel on board, personnel injuries, parking spot number, tail number "]},{"question":"31. The maximum vertical height of a load to be jettisoned is _____ inches measured from the _____ of the pallet\/platform.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 3 -474(N)]","responses":["78; bottom ","96; top ","100; bottom ","118; top "]},{"question":"32. During cargo jettison, ensure all selected lock annunciators are _____ before stating \"LOCKS RELEASED\".","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 3 -476(W)]","responses":["indicating locked ","flashing ","blank ","flashing or blank "]},{"question":"33. During a ditching, do not activate the _____ prior to the aircraft coming to a rest.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 3 -495(W)]","responses":["EPOS ","FEDS hatches ","Ramp Blowdown ","Emergency Locator Transmitter "]},{"question":"34. [COSA] The _____ and _____ ICS panels\/Headset Receptacle Panels are not operative when on emergency or battery power.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 1 -1770 (N)]","responses":["Pilot\/Copilot ","ACM\/Crew Rest ","FWD LM\/AFT LM ","FWD LM\/Crew Rest "]},{"question":"35. The maximum cargo weight that can be loaded left or right of aircraft center line is _____ pounds, provided all aircraft limitations are complied with.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 5 -80]","responses":["65,000","88,000","91,000","93,000 "]},{"question":"36. Without [STRUT IMP]; in the event the stabilizer strut system fails to operate properly, do not recycle the STAB STRUTS switch. Immediately _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 2 -937(C)]","responses":["proceed with manual operations of the stabilizer strut system ","remove hydraulic power and notify maintenance ","close the DOOR Solenoid Valve Handle to prevent damage to the aircraft ","open the DOOR Solenoid Valve Handle to prevent damage to the aircraft "]},{"question":"37. Without [STRUT IMP]; when retracting and stowing the stabilizer struts, prior to pulling the DOOR solenoid valve handle and rotating it clockwise to the CLOSED position, ensure both struts are fully retracted in the vertical position.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 2 -939]","responses":["TRUE ","FALSE "]},{"question":"38. Do not use _____ cargo compartment lighting in flight. PA system speakers\/volume will be deactivated during any condition that activates the cargo compartment lights because of sidewall oxygen\t \t system deployment. The speakers\/volume must be manually reactivated to make PA announcements.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 1 -602(C)]","responses":["emergency ","NVG ","SECURE ","incandescent red "]},{"question":"39. A handle assembly is installed at the forward loadmaster\u2019s station to manually override the _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 1 -724A]","responses":["Outflow valve ","Skin heat exchanger check valve ","Ground inlet shutoff valve ","Augmentation valve "]},{"question":"40. With ambient temperatures are at or below - 9 \u00b0C (15 \u00b0F), the AUX pumps may not initially generate full pressure. If system pressure does not rise to at least 3500 psi within 30 seconds of selecting the pump to\t AUTO, select the pump to off, wait 30 seconds and proceed as follows.1. Select the AUX pump to AUTO for 30 seconds, then off for 30 seconds.2. Repeat _____ or until system pressure indicates at least\t \t 3500 psi.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 [Para. 7 -122]","responses":["for a maximum of 5 cycles","for a minimum of 5 cycles","for a maximum of 10 cycles","for a minimum of 10 cycles"]},{"question":"41. If a centerline seat assembly cannot be secured with _____ serviceable floor attachment fittings, that seat module shall not be installed.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 3 -36(N)]","responses":["2","3","4","5 "]},{"question":"42. Vehicle single axle weights equal to or greater than _____ pounds must be loaded within 8 inches of the aircraft centerline in compartments D, F and G.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Fig. 4D -10 S1]","responses":["15,001","22,001","27,001","36,000 "]},{"question":"43. Vehicle single axle weights equal to or greater than _____ pounds must be loaded within 8 inches of the aircraft centerline in compartment E.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Fig. 4D -10 S1]","responses":["22,001","23,000","27,001","36,000 "]},{"question":"44. The maximum vehicle weight of a tracked vehicle with articulated suspension loaded in E compartment is _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Fig. 4D -17S2]","responses":["130,000","135,000","165,000","170,900"]},{"question":"45. Tracked vehicles with articulated suspension and with wheel weights exceeding _____ lbs (average) must be loaded within 8 inches of aircraft centerline","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Fig. 4D -17S1 (N]","responses":["2,000","5,000","7,500","9,000 "]},{"question":"46. Tunner loader furnished bridge plates shall not be used when loading\/offloading rolling stock from a K - loader with the ramp toes installed.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4B -11(C)]","responses":["TRUE ","FALSE "]},{"question":"47. Hazardous cargo considered jettisonable _____ be positioned forward of non-jettisonable cargo, except when its size, weight, and location will permit jettison by hand.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 5 -9]","responses":["should not ","could not ","can not ","shall not "]},{"question":"48. _____ highlight essential operating procedure, practice, condition or statement, etc which if not strictly observed could result in damage to, or destruction of equipment or loss of mission effectiveness.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 1 -42 (C)]","responses":["Warnings ","Cautions ","Notes ","Boldface items "]},{"question":"49. Do not connect exhausts from low temperature materials to thev _____ side vents or exhausts from operating engines to the _____ side vents. Connection of a low temperature exhaust to a vent\t contaimated with oil or grease may cause an explosion.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Fig. 2 -11 (W)]","responses":["left\/right ","right\/left ","left or right ","left\/left "]},{"question":"50. When cargo projects aft of the end of the logistics rails (FS_____), ensure the ramp toes do not contact the cargo while being raised to the vertical position.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 2 -33(C)]","responses":["1321","1390","1403","1424 "]},{"question":"51. When pedestal shoring is used under the Ramp Ground Support Pad for special loads, the shoring shall be a minimum of _____ inches long and _____ inches wide.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 2 -66]","responses":["30\/30","20\/18","18\/18","18\/30 "]},{"question":"52. The aft end of the ramp toes shall not be supported when in the _____ position.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 2 -69]","responses":["low ","high ","low or high ","the ramp toe shall never be supported "]},{"question":"53. When winching a vehicle with pneumatic tires up the cargo ramp at a 15 degree angle, a single line winching configuration has a limit of _____ pounds.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Table 4E -1]","responses":["20,000","22,303","10,000","15,000 "]},{"question":"54. When winching and the direction of pull is changed, the sheave _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 2 -137]","responses":["can be realigned with the RWC ","will automatically realign to the new direction ","is realigned by selecting the #3 hydraulic pump to ON ","must be manually realigned to the new direction "]},{"question":"55. In flight, the ramp toes will be _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 2 -70]","responses":["stowed ","installed and raised to the up (vertical overcenter) position ","stowed or installed and raised to the up (vertical overcenter) position ","installed in any position "]},{"question":"56. Palletized seat assemblies may be loaded in the logistic rails when transported as cargo. Passengers will not occupy palletized seats in the logistic rails.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 3 -48]","responses":["TRUE ","FALSE "]},{"question":"57. On aeromedical evacuation missions with litter or ambulatory patients, the ramp is restricted _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4B -7]","responses":["from carrying any cargo ","to loose baggage and floor loaded items only ","to two pallets in the left or right logistic rails ","to two pallets in the ADS rails or centerline floor loaded items "]},{"question":"58. Pallets or pallet trains up to _____ lbs per pallet may be loaded into the logistics rail system provided at least two locks, one left and one right are engaged in each pallet.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4C -11]","responses":["7,800","8,000","10,355","20,710 "]},{"question":"59. The ramp loadable height capability varies between _____ at the ramp hinge to _____ inches at the end of the ramp.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"T.O. 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4A -25]","responses":["156, 116","148, 128","138, 96","162, 112 "]},{"question":"60. Spotters are required to observe clearances and to prevent contact with the wing box structure when loading cargo higher than _____ inches forward of FS _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"T.O. 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4D -7(N)]","responses":["148; 937 ","158; 1165 ","162; 1074 ","148; 1074 "]},{"question":"61. When loading ISU containers that are 90 inches or higher into the logistic rails on the aircraft ramp, _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"T.O. 1C -17A -9 [Para. 6F -74]","responses":["jack the aircraft until the ramp height is greater than 68 inches","all vertical restrain shall be achieved using chain type tiedown","ramp toes with rollers and guide rails shall be installed","ADS links shall be installed"]},{"question":"62. The primary method of loading pallets into the ADS and logistic rail system is using the ramp toes.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"T.O. 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4C -53]","responses":["True ","False "]},{"question":"63. Due to limited maneuvering space, pallet rotation shall be closely supervised. Failure to comply could result in personnel injury or damage to the _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"T.O. 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4C -57(W)]","responses":["loading vehicle ","pallet rings ","pallet nets ","aircraft "]},{"question":"64. Required restraint for cargo on the pallet\/pallet train shall be provided using nets, tiedown straps, or chains. When supplemental restraint is required, additional tiedowns may be attached to the pallet or cargo floor.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"T.O. 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4C -13]","responses":["True ","False "]},{"question":"65. Straps and chains shall not be mixed to restrain cargo in the same direction. However, 10,000 and 25,000 pound rated devices with the appropriate chains may be used for a given direction of restraint.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"T.O. 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4B -35]","responses":["True ","False "]},{"question":"66. Netted two pallet trains that exceed _____ shall be restrained to the cargo floor.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4C -24]","responses":["96 inches ","10,355 pounds ","98 inches ","20,710 pounds "]},{"question":"67. Pallets or pallet trains up to 7,800 pounds per pallet may be loaded into the ADS rail\/lock system when","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4C -12]","responses":["at least two ADS locks (one left and one right) are engaged in each pallet. ","at least four ADS locks two left and two right) are engaged in each pallet. ","all longitudinal restraint is attached to the cargo floor. ","additional longitudinal restraint is attached to the cargo floor. "]},{"question":"68. Ensure cargo is restrained in _____ prior to raising and closing the ramp when cargo is positioned on the ramp for flight. Failure to comply could result in damage to the aircraft and cargo.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4B -11(C)]","responses":["the forward direction ","the aft direction ","both directions ","all directions "]},{"question":"69. When properly installed on a single pallet, the nets provide all necessary restraint for cargo loads up to _____pounds when the height of stacked cargo does not exceed 96 inches.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4C -21]","responses":["5,000","8,000","10,000","12,500"]},{"question":"70. The maximum wheel load on each ramp toe in the low position is _____pounds.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4B -13]","responses":["5,000","10,000","20,000","10,355 "]},{"question":"71. The maximum pallet\/platform weight on two ramp toes is _____pounds except for 18 -foot type VI platforms which may be increased to 14,500 pounds.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4B -13]","responses":["9,500","10,000","10,355","10,500 "]},{"question":"72. The maximum single axle load on the toes in the low position is _____pounds.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4B -13]","responses":["5,000","7,500","10,000","10,355 "]},{"question":"73. Replace the cargo winch cable if _____ or more broken wires per strand inch or _____ or more broken wires per cable inch are found.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4E -14]","responses":["2; 4 ","3; 7 ","4; 7 ","5; 8"]},{"question":"74. Vehicles with transmissions that are not equipped with a neutral position shall be loaded\/offloaded using the cargo winch.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4E -15(C)]","responses":["TRUE ","FALSE "]},{"question":"75. Two or three pallet train weight for cargo secured with nets and stacked to 96 inches shall not exceed _____pounds.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4C -24]","responses":["21,000","23,000","26,000","30,000 "]},{"question":"76. Two or three pallet train weight for cargo secured with nets and stacked above 96 inches (not to exceed 100 inches) shall not exceed _____ pounds.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4C -24]","responses":["20,710","21,000","26,000","27,000 "]},{"question":"77. All vehicle winching must be closely monitored by a crew of at least _____ personnel.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4E -20]","responses":["2","3","4","5 "]},{"question":"78. When low profile cargo does not permit the use of side nets, the top net may be used by itself provided the\t \t cargo weight does not exceed _____ pounds and cargo height does not exceed _____ inches from the pallet surface.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4C -29]","responses":["4,000; 25 ","4,000; 45 ","2,500; 25 ","2,500; 45 "]},{"question":"80. When plywood barriers and chain bridles are installed for forward restraint on palletized cargo, pallets that exceed \t _____ inches in height will have a minimum of _____ bridle(s) installed and the minimum thickness for the barrier will be _____ inches.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4C -37]","responses":["20; 1; 1\/2 ","30; 2; 3\/4 ","35; 3; 3\/4 ","40; 3; 1\/2 "]},{"question":"81. If _____ stowage pins are not engaged on _____ side of each toe stowed on the cargo door, that toe may come loose during flight.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 3 -27(W)]","responses":["upper; both left and right ","upper; either left or right ","lower; both left and right ","lower; either left or right "]},{"question":"82. When loading pallets that exceed a height of 100 inches, monitor overhead clearances between the top of pallets and aircraft structure. When positioning MHE in preparation for loading 463L pallets into the logistic rail system, contact with the aircraft shall be considered.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4C -43(C)]","responses":["door ","strakes ","center wing box ","lower rudder and tail cone "]},{"question":"83. A chain bridle provides restraint in _____ direction(s.)","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4B -31]","responses":["only the forward or aft ","more than one ","only one ","all "]},{"question":"84. The maximum number of empty 463L pallets that may be stacked for airlift, excluding the base support pallet is ____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4C -41]","responses":["5","10","15","20 "]},{"question":"85. During palletized cargo loading (non-winching), the minimum distance between the aircraft ramp\/toes and K - loader is _____ inches.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4C -53(C)]","responses":["2","4","6","8 "]},{"question":"86. Tiedown devices connected to cargo that spans from the main cargo floor to the ramp shall be _____ prior to opening the ramp.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4B -48(C)]","responses":["connected ","tightened ","removed ","loosened "]},{"question":"87. The minimum thickness of rolling shoring shall be _____ inch(es).","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4B -66]","responses":["1\/2","3\/4","1","1 1\/2 "]},{"question":"88. With the ramp toes in the high position, the required overlap between the ramp toe contact pads and the floor of the loader is _____ inches.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Table 4B -1(C)]","responses":["4","6","8","11 "]},{"question":"89. In the high position the ramp toes should be at an angle which causes the aft end of the toe to be above coplanar position with the ramp floor.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Table 4B -1(C)]","responses":["TRUE ","FALSE "]},{"question":"90. When using a tiedown strap to secure a ramp toe on the cargo door, route the strap around the stowage rack and secure the strap to the rack.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 3 -28(W)]","responses":["TRUE ","FALSE "]},{"question":"91. Each tiedown ring can accommodate a maximum of _____ CGU-1\/B tiedown straps for any directional pull calculations.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4B -45]","responses":["three ","four ","five ","six "]},{"question":"92. When attaching multiple chains\/devices to one tiedown ring, the ring _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -9 [Para. 4B -44]","responses":["can be used for restraint in only one direction","can be used for restraint in only two directions","cannot be used for both forward and aft restraint","cannot be used for both vertical and lateral restraint "]},{"question":"93. Crewmembers occupying a crew station will have an oxygen mask connected and readily available for use from _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"AFI 11- 2C-17 V3 [Para. 6.27.1.1]","responses":["before engine start until engine shutdown. ","before engine start until landing. ","after engine start until engine shutdown ","takeoff until landing "]},{"question":"94. Crewmembers may travel as MEP for a maximum of _____ hours.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"AFI 11- 2C17V3 [Para. 3.7.4]","responses":["16","18","24","30 "]},{"question":"95. When children under the age of _____ are accepted as passengers, their sponsor has the option to either hold the child or place him\/her in a DOT approved ICS.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"AFI 11 -2C -17V3 [Para. 13.4.2.5]","responses":["six ","four ","two ","three "]},{"question":"96. Use of non- mission related material is prohibited by any crewmember during any critical phase of flight. All non-mission related material will be stowed prior to _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"AFI 11 -2C -17 V3 [Para. 5.2.1]","responses":["Descent Checklist ","Preflight ","Takeoff ","All of the above "]},{"question":"97. MEP crewmembers will not retain custody of ammunition on an aircraft.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"AFI 11- 2C-17 V3 [Para. 7.7.4.1]","responses":["TRUE ","FALSE "]},{"question":"98. An entry will be placed in AFTO 781A when the aircraft is _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"AFI 11 -2C -17 V3 [Para. 6.45.1, 6.45.2]","responses":["operated on a Semi -Prepared Runway ","sprayed with insecticide; aerosol d -phenothrin- 2 percent (or equivalent.) ","flown over water, under 1,000 feet above sea level for longer than 30 minutes ","both A and C "]},{"question":"99. When wearing the ACDE, Atropine and 2 PAM Chloride auto injectors will be kept in the _____ ACDE pocket. If the integrated survival vest\/body armor is worn, the Atropine and 2 PAM Chloride auto injectors may be kept in the _____ flight suit pocket.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"AFI 11 -2C -17 V3 [Para. 10.4.5]","responses":["upper right, lower right","upper left, lower right","lower right, upper left","lower left, upper left"]},{"question":"100. The aircraft loadmaster may deviate from load plans to facilitate ease of onload or offload of cargo, accommodate additional passengers, and to alleviate unnecessary aircraft reconfiguration without submitting documentation.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"AFI 11 -2C -17 V3 [Para. 13.2.1.3E]","responses":["TRUE ","FALSE "]},{"question":"101. Personnel will only be permitted to carry their basic combat load or individual issue of hazardous material when _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"AFI 11 -2C -17 V3 [Para. 13.11.4.2.1]","responses":["The combat load or hazmat is carried in their rucksack","The combat load or hazmat is correctly marked and certified with a shipperu2019s declaration","Given to the loadmaster before takeoff","They will engage an enemy force immediately upon arrival"]},{"question":"102. The maximum altitude for emergency airlift of personnel will not exceed flight level _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"AFI 11 -2C -17 V3 [Para. 17.5.5]","responses":["100","150","200","250 "]},{"question":"103. Maximum altitude for floor loaded patients is flight level _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"AFI 11- 2C-17 V3 [Para. 20.15.1]","responses":["130","180","250","350 "]},{"question":"104. When _____ or more passengers\/troops are planned, a pallet position shall be left open to accommodate palletized\/floor loaded baggage.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"AFI 11 -2C -17 V3 [Para. 13.4.2.1.1]","responses":["10","20","40","53 "]},{"question":"105. The following smoke detectors are required for home station\/main operating base departures: One AV, all 4 IRU, _____ plus two others in the cargo compartment.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"AFI 11 -2C -17 V3 [Table 4.1]","responses":["CAR 1, 2, 10, 11 ","CAR 5, 6, 7, 8 ","CAR 1, 2, 13, 14 ","CAR 9, 10, 13, 14 "]},{"question":"106. All passenger hand-carried items must be of a size to fit under the seat and must not obstruct the safety aisle. Any item that does not fit under a seat or obstructs an aisle way will be ____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"AFI 11 -2C -17 V3 [Para. 13.3.1]","responses":["downloaded and transported on the next available aircraft","stowed with checked baggage and secured for flight","turned over to TMO\/ITO for proper manifesting","secured with a carabineer clip to the sidewall"]},{"question":"107. If no maintenance personnel are available and crew duties limit the availability of a crewmember, the engines may be started without someone outside the aircraft. If this option is used, ensure all\t \t crewmembers are thoroughly briefed.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"11 -2C -17 V3 [Para. 5.33]","responses":["TRUE ","FALSE "]},{"question":"108. The maximum FDP for a basic aircrew is _____ hours, (_____ hours when the autopilot is inoperative).","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"AFI 11- 2C-17 V3 [Para. 3.7.1.1]","responses":["2\/16","16\/12","24\/12","4\/16 "]},{"question":"109. The maximum crew duty time for a basic aircrew is _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"AFI 11 -2C -17 V3 [Para. 3.7.2]","responses":["24 hours ","20 hours ","18 hours ","12 hours "]},{"question":"110. Maximum CDT for an augmented aircrew is _____ hours.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"AFI 11 -2C -17 V3 [Para. 3.7.2]","responses":["16+45 ","24+15 ","24+45 ","26+15 "]},{"question":"111. For all missions, the latest allowable alert time is _____ hours after the expected alert time.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"AFI 11- 2C-17 V3 [Para. 3.11.2.2]","responses":["2","4","6","10 "]},{"question":"112. Do not taxi an aircraft within_____ of obstructions without wing walkers monitoring clearance between aircraft and obstructions. With wing walkers, avoid taxi obstructions by at least_____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"AFI 11 -2C -17 V3 [Para. 5.19.1]","responses":["25 yards; 10 yards ","10 yards; 25 yards ","25 feet; 10 feet ","10 feet; 25 feet "]},{"question":"113. During reverse taxi operations, obstacles greater than _____ tall require _____ of clearance from the aft end of the ramp in coplanar.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"AFI 11- 2C-17 V3 [Fig. 5.1]","responses":["8 feet; 25 feet ","8 feet; 88 feet ","10 feet; 25 feet ","10 feet; 88 feet "]},{"question":"114. If taxiing on very narrow taxiways, a good technique according to AFTTP 3 -3.C -17 is to _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"AFTTP 3 -3.C -17 [Para. 3.2.3.5.4]","responses":["deplane a wing walker to monitor clearances ","instruct the flying crew chief to watch clearances ","place a loadmaster in each troop door to call out distances ","use the Drogue Parachute Video System to visually monitor the taxiway centerline "]},{"question":"115. The AFTTP 3 -3.C -17 \u201cpaint a picture\u201d technique for loadmasters involves _____ the backing operation.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"AFTTP 3 -3.C -17 [A7.7.2.4]","responses":["giving descriptive information needed to increase pilot situational awareness during ","drawing a simple diagram of the taxi plan on paper before beginning ","marking taxiway edges with chemical light devices just before ","drawing a reference line on the taxiway with chalk prior to "]},{"question":"116. The critical side is situation dependent and may vary based on _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"AFTTP 3 -3.C -17 [Para. 3.2.4.5 ]","responses":["Proximity of wheels to runway\/taxiway edge, obstacles, or FOD potential ","Perception of the Aircraft Commander ","Proximity of the closest obstacle ","Perception of the Loadmaster "]},{"question":"117. When backing, the effective aircraft gross weight can increase up to an additional _____ pounds and possibly exceed maximum allowable ramp weights.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"AFTTP 3 -3.C -17 [Para. 3.2.4]","responses":["29,000","50,000","89,000","100,000"]}]}
